liweddings.com 2014-06-25

# LIWeddings.com Internet Privacy Policy

###  Long Island Weddings Vendors ▼

| 

Long Island Weddings ™, Inc ("LIWeddings.com") has developed this privacy statement for you, the visitor, to demonstrate our commitment to privacy on the Internet. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.LIWeddings.com and all other Web sites owned and operated by LIWeddings.com.

LIWeddings.com can be contacted by mail at:

Attention Legal Department  
Long Island Weddings ™, Inc.  
3245 Route 112  
Suite 5  
Medford, NY 11763  
United States of America

by phone at (631) 320-3450 or

by e-mail _here_.

1\. Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors

LIWeddings.com may collect and/or track (1) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, and type of Web browser of visitors to LIWeddings.com' Web site, (2) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with LIWeddings.com via e-mail, (3) information knowingly provided by the visitor in online forms, registration forms, surveys, and contest entries (including demographic and personal profile data), and (4) aggregate and user-specific information on which pages visitors access.

LIWeddings.com may place Internet "cookies" on visitor's hard drives. Internet cookies save data about individual visitors, such as the visitorís name, password, user-name, shopping cart, screen preferences, the pages of a site viewed by the visitor, and the advertisements viewed or clicked by the visitor. When the visitor revisits LIWeddings.com' Web site, LIWeddings.com may recognize the visitor by the Internet cookie and customize the visitor's experience accordingly. Visitors may decline Internet cookies, if any, by using the appropriate feature of their Web client software, if available.

When a visitor performs a search within LIWeddings.com' Web site, LIWeddings.com may record information identifying the visitor or linking the visitor to the search performed. LIWeddings.com may also record limited information for every search request and uses that information only to solve technical problems with the service and to calculate overall usage statistics.

2\. Use of Personal Data Collected

Personal data collected by LIWeddings.com may be used by LIWeddings.com for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of usersí behavior, for product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements, or to customize the content and layout of LIWeddings.com' site. Aggregate data on visitorsí home servers may be used for internal purposes or provided to third parties such as advertisers. Individually identifying information, such as names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone numbers, and other personal information which visitors voluntarily provide to LIWeddings.com may be (i) added to LIWeddings.com' databases and used for future calls and mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and status of orders placed online, or (ii) provided to reputable third parties who provide products and services which LIWeddings.com believes that visitors may be interested in purchasing or obtaining, with prior notice to the visitor. LI Wedding

3\. Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties

Any third party to which LIWeddings.com shares, rents, sells, or otherwise discloses personal data will be under a contractual obligation to use the personal data for marketing products and services which LIWeddings.com determines, in its sole judgment, that visitors might find of interest. LIWeddings.com will use its reasonable efforts to identify such third parties who may have products or services of interest to visitors to LIWeddings.com' site. However, such parties are independent third parties over which LIWeddings.com exercises no control, and therefore LIWeddings.com is not responsible for their conduct, products, or services, and will not be liable therefor. LIWeddings.com will disclose to third parties only information in aggregate form, that is publicly available, and/or that is knowingly and voluntarily disclosed by visitors. If there are advertisements on LIWeddings.com' Web site, through the use of third party cookies, the advertiser(s) will be electronically notified when visitors view or click on its advertisements.

4\. Security Measures

LIWeddings.com has implemented numerous security features to prevent the unauthorized release of or access to personal information. In particular, when a visitor places an order on this site (if any) or accesses his or her account information (if any), LIWeddings.com offers the visitor the ability to use a secure server. The secure server encrypts all information a visitor inputs before it is sent to LIWeddings.com, and is also used to securely store personal information. Please be advised, however, that while LIWeddings.com has endeavored to create a secure and reliable site for visitors, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to/from LIWeddings.com via this site or e-mail cannot be guaranteed. Accordingly, LIWeddings.com is not responsible for the security of information transmitted via the Internet. [For more private communication, visitors can contact us by telephone at (631)331-5703.]

5\. Opt-Out Right

Visitors may opt out of having their personal information collected by LIWeddings.com, used by LIWeddings.com for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by LIWeddings.com or third parties to send promotional correspondences to the visitor, by contacting LIWeddings.com via postal mail, e-mail, or telephone at the addresses above, or by checking the appropriate box. LI Wedding

6\. Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data

Upon request via postal mail, e-mail, or phone, LIWeddings.com will provide to visitors a summary of any personal information retained by LIWeddings.com regarding the visitor. Visitors may modify, correct, change or update their personal record or cause their personal record to be removed from LIWeddings.com' database. LIWeddings.com will only send personal records to the e-mail address on file for the visitor name associated with it.

7\. Collection of Personal Data from Children

To the extent LIWeddings.com is able to determine the age of users by their submissions to or communications with LIWeddings.com' Web site, LIWeddings.com will not knowingly (i) collect or post information from individuals under the age of sixteen ("children") without their parentís or guardianís consent, or (ii) provide any personally identifying information collected from children, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. If registration is required for any services on the LIWeddings.com Site, and a user submits information to LIWeddings.com' Web site as part of the registration process which indicates that such user is a child, the childís parent or guardian will receive an e-mail alerting them to the childís registration and providing instructions on how the parent can delete the childís registration, if so desired. No information collected through LIWeddings.com' Web site from users self- identified as children will knowingly be used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside LIWeddings.com. If there are no age restrictions on a contest which requires registration, and if a child wins, notification and prizes will be sent to the parent(s) or guardian(s) identified in the initial registration process.

8\. LIWeddings.com's Right to Contact User

LIWeddings.com reserves the right to contact site visitors regarding account status and changes to the subscriber agreement, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors.

9\. LIWeddings.com's Right to Change Privacy Policy

The foregoing policy is effective as of December 11, 1995. LIWeddings.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy. By entering the LIWeddings.com website you are accepting all terms and conditions outlined in the above Long Island Weddings ™, Inc Internet Privacy Policy.  
  
---|---
